leeschools.net 2016-05-13

# Privacy Policy - Lee County School District

We recognize the importance of protecting your privacy and the information that you share with us. Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the highest-quality products and services with the highest level of integrity. It is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide and to help you in making informed decisions when using our site, products and services. This Privacy Policy will be continually assessed against new technologies and our schools needs.

**Collection of Information**

We collect personally identifiable information you voluntarily choose to disclose and aggregate information that is automatically collected when you visit the web site. The information that we collect from you will vary depending on how you choose to contact us. If you contact us via e-mail or submit an online request for information, we will collect the information that you provide to us in your e-mail message or request, including your name, contact information, e-mail address and any questions or comments that you may submit.

We use third-party tools that captures detailed information about how users interact with our site and what pages they visit. The data we collect from these tools are used internally to better understand and support our users. We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous.

**Use of Information**

Your personal information is used to process your request for program information and help match your interests. We may store your information and send you updates on your program and our school. We also use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer service, and making other products and services available to our customers and prospective customers.

**Security**

We use industry standard security measures to protect any personal information that you may provide to us. However, we cannot guarantee that your submissions to our website, any content residing on our servers, or any transmissions from our server will be completely secure.
